[music]
You shout it out, but I can't hear a
word you [music] say. [singing]
I'm talking loud, not saying much.
[music] I'm criticized,
but all your bullets ricochet.
You shoot me down, but
[music and singing] I get up.
I'm bulletproof. Nothing to lose. Fire
[music] away. Fire away. Ricochet. You
take your aim. Fire away. [music]
Fire [singing] away. You shoot me down,
but I won't fall. I am Titanium. [music]
You shoot me down, but I won't fall. I
am Titania.
Yeah, you cut me down. But it's you who
[music] have to [singing] fall.
Ghost town and haunted [music] love.
Raise your voice. [music] Sticks and
[singing] stones may break my bones. I'm
talking loud, not saying much.
Bulletproof, nothing to lose. Fire away,
fire [singing] away. Ricochet, you take
your aim. Fire away, fire away. You
[music] shoot me down, but I won't fall.
I am Titania.
You shoot me down, [music and singing]
but I won't fall. I am Titan.
>> [music]
[applause]
>> Cheese and crackers. I made so much
money I forgot I got work today. My name
is Apple Bottom and a month ago I was
dumped by my long-term boyfriend, a
Pegasus [music] called Care Package. and
it was the best damn thing to ever
[music] happen to me. You never realize
how much you miss the no strings
attached life until you finally get it
back. Now that I've got my routine
together, I'm living without all the
drama and headaches. I'm [music] back on
my meds, so I'm not hearing the voices
so much lately. I'm making more money
than ever, and I'm being [music] a
productive member of society. Life's
never felt this good. But then, why do I
[music] feel all empty inside when I get
back home every night? You know, I do
always think you look your happiest when
you're wearing your girl clothes.
>> Hey, cousin Apple Bottom. I'm here for
that steaming hot night of lustfilled
passion we've been talking about. I
don't want to do it anymore. You can't
do me like that. I walked all the
>> I love you. Aha. Yes. Jolly good. Quite
right. Quite right indeed.
>> Excuse me. This is Care Package. He
recently entered the adoption agency
since his father was murdered. Isn't
that right, Care Package?
We think he's still struggling to
regulate his emotions since the trauma
of seeing his dad killed right in front
of him. So, we're going to have him
start recording a video diary and [__]
Do you have anything to say for your
very first entry? Care package?
>> Hey, P. It's Care Package again. I told
you I'd do it. I finally finished grade
school. This is my graduation cap I wore
at the graduation ceremony. I'm going to
set it here right on top. So, you can
try wearing it, too. Every other pony in
class had their parents show up, so it
was rather unfortunate not having you
there. But because I didn't have anybody
trying to take pictures, I was able to
beat the crowds and get out early.
It's grim to say, but I guess there are
benefits to you being dead after all.
Dad, I got a job. I am officially a male
pony starting today. I don't usually
wander far from home, so I'll probably
be seeing lots of new places on my
routes. I did the math, and after just 2
months of delivering mail, I'll start
making enough bits to rent out the
apartment you took me to when I was
first adopted.
Hey, Dad. I killed another pony today.
This one was kind of sloppy. So, I think
the police ponies are going to come and
get me again. I'm sure there's not
enough proof to put me behind bars for
too long, but I can't really come up
with a good alibi for this one. So, I've
been spending a lot of days lately at
the psych ward. I will probably be going
back there for a little bit. Don't
expect me to record another vlog for the
next couple weeks.
I think this is the first year I forgot
the anniversary of your death. But I've
got a good reason. I swear I met the
most wonderful pony. His name is Apple
Bottom, but he goes by Apple Split
because he's autistic and wonderfully
schizophrenic and so he might just be
the easiest pony to manipulate. He's an
Earth pony and he's a part of the Apple
family, so I'm assuming incredibly
inbred, too. But he is also incredibly
handsome. I never did tell you I like
stallions, but then again, I was so
young when I had killed you, I probably
didn't even know this about myself at
the time. Ponyville is a dreadfully
homophobic place under Celestia's reign.
That will never change. I don't like it.
When I'm around Apple Bottom, however,
it's like we can just be in our own
little world where no pony can judge us.
It's nice to put it simply.
>> Hey, [__] I clogged the toilet again.
>> Bloody hell, I'll grab the plunger. No,
I mean it's not clogged in this very
moment. I already fixed it by smooshing
it down with my hoof. That's how we do
things on the farm. Hey, go open me a
can of raviolis, [__] Mama's got to
eat.
>> Ah, the little earth pony is still here.
What is it now? Day 30 since you've
refused to move out of my apartment.
>> Where were you all night?
>> Where do you think I was finishing up my
mail deliveries?
>> You're covered in blood. You killed some
pony, didn't you? Without me. What about
doing that stuff together?
>> Excuse me. Pray. Tell again why we must
continue to do anything together when
we're not dating anymore. You know, you
are quite lucky to have dated a pony
like me who is generous enough to lend
you his hospitality after you've broken
up with him.
>> You're the one who broke up with me.
Also, I don't have to be here. You know,
I'm making so much money on the farm
that I can move out whenever I want.
>> Then grow a pair and do it. Good. Quite
right. Quite right indeed.
>> I'm going to draw you giving birth.
>> Make it look sublime.
>> By the way, my cousin Brayburn and his
stupid husband Saurin will be coming
over soon for dinner.
>> How fun. I'll pull out the fancy
silverware. You seriously made all this
cousin apple bottom.
>> When you're both black and an earth
pony, you have to find ways to prove
your worth because other ponies are
going to judge you at first glance. My
way is proving that I can be a
submissive housewife.
>> Your Salsbury steak is still frozen in
the middle. I think it needs another
minute in the microwave.
>> It's fine.
>> No, let him suffer, Saurin. I want you
both to be here [music] when he finally
admits that he needs me way more than I
need him. If you would like to have a
sample of the food I lovingly prepared
for my family, all you have to do is
ask. I have taken care of myself well
into adulthood just fine. Thank you.
>> Hey Brayburn, can you ask now?
>> Oh yeah. Hey Apple Split. Saurin wanted
to know if he could.
I wanted to know if I could film a
mukbang for Saurin's YouTube channel. I
mean my YouTube channel. We'd just be
putting my phone in the middle of the
table. You wouldn't be on screen or
anything.
>> Do what you want.
Can I dip my corn dog in your mashed
potatoes?
>> Oh, yeah. You can do that.
You have to fart.
Can't you just hold it? We just started.
Okay, but do it quietly so that the
camera doesn't pick it up. Was
that too loud? It's fine.
>> Apple Bottom, mind telling your cousin
not to blast a fat one while we are at
the dinner table?
>> Mind not trying to dictate when my
cousin is allowed to fart?
>> It is my house we're in, so I believe I
have the right.
>> Wait, is that my magic knife you're
eating with?
>> It sure is. The blood of all your
previous victims mixes in well with the
pre-made Salbury steak sauce.
>> Give it to me. Will you beg for it?
>> It's mine.
>> It belongs to me.
>> You can't leave when we're having a nice
family dinner.
>> You don't want your mentally ill cousin
running around with sharp
>> object mine right now.
>> It's been like this between us for a
whole month.
>> Why did the two of you break up anyway?
>> Okay, so you know how Care Package is a
serial killer? [music]
>> I was kind of hoping he would have
stopped doing that stuff since it makes
us complicit by not going to the police.
I think that side of him is so cool and
beautiful and [music] it sucks balls
that nobody but me gets to see it. So, I
just want to make ourselves public and
tell everyone and go on the run and be
all famous, but he wants to keep it
behind closed doors like we're a disease
on society just cause [music] we kill
people.
>> Okay. Yes. So, it's your fault.
>> Have you thought that maybe it's because
he doesn't want to go to jail?
>> That's what he says.
>> The possibility of imprisonment is a
valid concern for a horse. What is he
doing now?
>> I don't know. Cutting up a body or
something. [music] Sometimes he'll bring
a body home and pose it like it's alive
cuz he finds it amusing before
dismembering it and throwing the parts
in the trash.
>> Why don't you come to my therapy class
tomorrow?
>> You go to therapy?
>> Saurin often goes because his mukbangs
don't get that many views on Pony Tube
[music] and I found it helps me too when
I go with him.
>> Get out of the car. I'm not asking
again.
>> I don't want to.
>> I'm paying the driver by the minute.
which I know you can afford with your
newfound wealth shaking your goods at
the Ponyville Jazz Club.
>> Now, just so every pony is aware, we are
going to have a special guest sitting in
with us this gathering. Miss Pinkie Pie
is a practicing psychologist.
>> Hi, every pony.
>> Pinkie Pie, quit being a godamn pick me.
We're only here to observe and learn.
I'm her handler. I'm sorry for her
interruption, Mrs. Redart. Why don't we
take turns introducing ourselves
starting from the left and working our
way down?
>> Hello every pony. My government-given
name is Apple Bottom, but I prefer to go
by Apple Split. I am a diagnosed
schizophrenic, so if I just randomly
start talking, it probably means I'm
talking to the voices in my head. I'm
weird and different and I'm gay. So, I'm
impossible to understand. And I am also
a sex addict who struggles to hold down
a meaningful relationship.
>> Yo, Apple Bottom, what's good?
>> I I I'm Sombra. I'm a gay sex addict as
well. I struggle from depression and
thoughts that lead me to wanting to unal
alive myself. And I I often find myself
going for almost exclusively for, you
know, straight guys. And I I'm here to
to learn to not do that.
>> I'm care package.
>> Hold on. I I don't like how no pony said
hi to me like they did for Apple Bottom.
I'm feeling like, you know, really
ignored right now. And
>> I said I go by Apple split.
>> Apple split. Yeah, cuz you're like
schizophrenic. We get it.
>> Hello, Sombra.
>> Okay, that's good. I I I'm satisfied
with that.
>> I'm Care Package. I'm white and gay and
I have also been diagnosed for a
multitude of mental health problems. I
too struggle to hold down a meaningful
relationship.
>> Hello, Care Package.
>> Sup, Care Package? You seem like someone
who would be like, you know, cool to
hang out with and stuff.
>> Um, good morning every pony. I'm Brayurn
and I'm a homosexual.
>> Starting to see a pattern here.
>> Well, Miss Redart, in the world of My
Little Pony, Stallion's rights and
privileges in Ponyville are
unfortunately only comparable to that of
a human woman.
>> Twilight, I really don't care because
I'm sexist.
>> I'm just here to support Saurin.
Legally, I can't say he's my husband
because gay marriage is outlawed in
Ponyville, but spiritually, he is.
Spiritually doesn't mean anything
because we're in the real world anyway.
Moving past introductions.
>> Hold on. I didn't get to introduce
myself.
>> Apple Bottom, you called earlier and
said you had something you wanted to
share with the group.
>> Oh, uh, yeah, I kind of do. This is a
drawing I drew of care package giving
birth to his and my kid. This is the
baby, but as an adult, it name is parcel
core, and it's what I call an oblivion
pony. That's a special kind of pony that
is even more special than an alicorn.
It's like a vampire where if it drinks
the blood of a unicorn, it gets all of
its powers. Also, Parcel Core is gay.
>> That's wonderful, Apple Bottom. Why
don't you ask the others to pass it
around so we can all have a look?
>> Twilight, when do I get to do something?
>> Pinkie Pie, no pony has ever liked you
from the moment you were born.
>> Pass it around.
>> No, I I don't feel like doing that.
>> You know what might fix your
relationship with Apple Bottom? Mr. care
package. If you and Apple Split went in
the bathroom down the hall and literally
right now,
>> Mrs. Redart, you can't legally tell your
clients to do something like that.
>> Twilight, it's between two stallions. It
barely even counts. Okay, while they are
doing that, we will Oh, no. They're done
already.
So, how do you feel? Any better care
package? You tell us first.
He says physical intimacy is not the
root of our problems.
>> Oh, I don't know what to do to help you
then. Anyway, our 3minut session is up.
That will be $180.
>> That place was a ripoff.
[crying]
>> We could always just go home and make up
by sharing a microwavable burrito.
Then stop breaking up with me. You're
the one who's doing it. If I had it my
way, we'd still be together. But you
can't stand the idea about being open
about who we are. Whether it's about you
proud of being a serial killer or about
us being gay in a homophobic society.
Screw society. Why does everything have
to be a secret with you?
Oh
my
goodness.
Oh,
[music]
Luna quickly called Twilight and her
pack of little lesbian [__]
>> An ollicorn of death.
>> Yes. A prophecy [music] was foretold
long ago that the olicorn of death would
appear one day while I'm taking a huge
[__] Luna and I just got word that
[music] every pony in Manhattan and lost
Pegasus are gone. That is over [music] 6
billion souls that just disappeared. I
would say maybe 0.2% of the world's
population remains.
>> Hold on. What do you mean by gone? You
know, they're [music] just gone. Oh my
god. Oh my god. Is right. My sister and
I [music] sense their presence coming
from nearby the local McDonald's about
half a mile from here. You girls must go
there and kill whoever it is before we
all explode. [music]
>> Why can't you handle it? That sounds
kind of crazy.
>> Did you even hear what I just said? It's
the ollicorn of death. Death is a
concept, not even a physical thing.
[music] I'm only the oicorn of the sun.
The sun is literally just a giant ball
of fire in space. How am I supposed to
beat that [__]
>> Why not Princess Luna?
>> I guess I can go with them. Let me just
go to my bedroom and grab my gun.
[music]
Care package.
[__] what did you just do? You know
you just killed [music] 99.8% of all
ponies. You're going to eradicate the
whole entire pony race at this point.
>> As the alicorn of death, I can bring a
pony to the end of their lifespan in an
instant.
>> Prove it.
Why the hell did you tell him to do
that? I had to make sure.
>> Whatever, nerd. Just stay out of my way
while I do something cool.
>> It cuts [music] through my heart. I'll
be chasing after you. [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> Cousin Apple Jack
[music]
Fluttershot. [music]
>> [music]
>> Where the hell are you taking me? Put me
down.
>> Doctor Who's Doctor Who's, are you home?
>> Don't break my window.
>> What have you been up to,
>> Sombra? I was on the toilet. You've been
ghosting me for 3 weeks after I sucked
your balls that one time. What gives?
>> I'm not gay.
>> No, I know you're not gay. That's why
I'm into you. I I know it's not healthy.
>> Sombra, my wife and daughter will be
home soon, and they can't know I shared
a bed with a black man. She's both
homophobic and super racist.
[music]
>> Celestia, girl, what's the tea? Oh my
god. Girl, you can can't be serious.
This is bananas. Yeah. Yeah, I'll be
over there in like 5 minutes. Can Can I
bring Doctor Who's too, girl? You know
the one. He's the handsome son of a
[__] with the blue eyes, who's like a
Doctor Who David tenant reference. Yeah.
Yeah, you can count on me.
>> What was that about?
>> Baby girl, you ain't got nothing to
worry about. Come on. We need to go
stand before Princess Celestia. She
wants us to go help vanquish an evil
alicorn or some [__]
>> Wo! It's really red out here. What? Oh,
yeah. Yeah, I guess it is, ain't it?
Yeah, [__] happens here. You can hop in
the basket on the front of my bike. It
will look pretty cute if you think about
it.
>> Where's the seat?
>> Yeah, don't got one. I got it from
Facebook Marketplace for like $13 and it
didn't come with a seat. So, it it's
fine. I don't really need a seat anyway.
>> How do you sit if there's no seat?
>> How do I sit on anything? Haha. You
know, the the bike peg just just goes up
in my ass.
>> What do you wish of us? Oh, great and
powerful Princess Celestia.
>> Okay, so you know Care Package. I have
never met that pony in my life.
>> Well, he has killed every member of the
main six except for Pinkie Pie. And we
are looking for replacements. Would you
like to be a member of the new main six?
Right now, it's me and Pinkie Pie. Keep
in mind, I am not giving you the choice.
If you say no, you will be killed.
>> Yeah, I can be one. I've got nothing
going on this weekend.
>> I knew I could trust you, David Tennant.
You are the only pony in all of
Equestria who has never once let me
down.
>> Okay. The six of us. Pinkie Pie, Sombra,
Dr. Hooves, and Oh [__] that's only
four. We need a sixth member.
>> Sorry, I thought this was the bathroom.
>> Big Mac, come over here.
>> This is still only five.
>> The only one who can defeat an Olly corn
is another Olly corn. And because I
don't feel like doing it myself, I ask,
which of you of the new main six is most
willing to give up their position as the
horse variant they are now? And ascend
to the rank of Ollyorn.
>> Me. Me. Pick me. I've always wanted to
have a real horn.
>> By the power of all three horses, I
hereby declare Dr. Hoves as Ollyorn.
>> I have a horn. I finally got a horn and
wings, too.
>> You know what? It's whatever. We got a
scadattlele.
>> Look, it's Princess Celestia herself.
>> She's here to save us from the alicorn
of death. Well, [__] We've got a [__]
ton of ponies to disappoint. Care
package? No. Ollicorn [music] of death.
I hope you are prepared for divine
punishment for erasing my beloved pupil
and booty call, Twilight [music]
Sparkle, from existence.
>> You are the one who sent her to me.
>> Care package? Look, I've finally got a
horn. I've got a real one. Now I don't
even need that knife anymore.
>> How did you get that?
>> Celestia gave me one so I can stop you
with it. But I'm not going to. I'm going
to use all that magic within it to make
sure we can live our best lives possible
and really be equals. If you have a
horn, then you really don't need me
anymore. How are we supposed to take
advantage of each other when we've both
got everything? We are not supposed to
be equals.
>> What is it you want from me then?
>> It's so much more simple than you're
making out to be. I just want you to say
you need me. You're supposed to be an
earth pony who's got nothing. I broke up
with you so that you'd come crawling
back to me.
>> Sombra now while he's distracted.
>> What? Oh, okay. Yeah. [applause]
[cheering]
night thinking about [music] me. My
sweet
can't see baby I know that me is my
[music] soul. Pull it up down
like Nintendo. See you can't [music] see
baby I know that me is my soul. I can't
relate
to desperation.
>> [music]
>> I give a [__]
are on vacation
and I got this one boy and he won't stop
calling when they act [music] this way.
I know I got him too.
[music]
>> Doctor Who's get under me.
>> No, that's gay.
>> No, not like in a gay way. I like made
an umbrella out of magic.
>> David Tennant. No, you're my favorite
Doctor Who out of like all 13 of them.
Get up. You can survive this. We're
going to get out of here together. Don't
you die on me. Oh, he's not coming back
from that.
>> Every pony run away from the falling
knight. I don't have a plan for this
situation. [screaming]
>> New main six group up under this awning.
Why are there only four?
>> Apple Bottom was one of the new main six
and so was Dr. Hooves and he just died.
>> Big Mac, do you have a plan? No. Pinky,
do you have a plan? You three really
suck as the new main six. Pinkie Pie
become a box of sunmade raisins.
>> Zombra, what is that thing you created?
>> I think I used the wrong spell on Apple
Bottom and Care Package. You know how me
and Doctor Who like did it 3 weeks ago?
>> I do not know about this.
>> Well, I was so pissed that he ghosted me
after that. I handcrafted a body
swapping spell to use on him as revenge
on him. I was going to body swap with
him and then jump off the side of a
cliff and then quickly body swap back so
he would like die and [__] But I think
because I hit both Apple Bottom and Care
Package with the spell at the same time
and also hit that drawing Apple Bottom
Duo of Care Package giving birth, I like
killed the two of them and brought their
M Craig baby to life. At least you know
that's what I think happened. I could be
way off.
[music]
My
soul see
that me is [music] the soul move it up
down
sleep
[music]
I meant to know secret baby I know that
is that sweet I guess so [music]
that's that
The time has come, blood breath. Tremble
before your inevitable doom, for the
lowclass Russian feline [__] janitor of
Equestria has arrived to clean up the
absolute mess you're going to be after I
kick your immortal ass back to the Hot
Topic from where you [music] crawled out
of. Saurin,
>> clean sweep. We may be rivals when it
comes to love because you keep trying to
sleep with my boyfriend Big Mac behind
my back, but I won't let you fight him.
>> This vampire [__] can just liquefy
anything. What the hell am I supposed to
do against that?
>> Oh, darling, I'm home from the mailing
station.
>> Welcome home, love. The food's almost
done. You wouldn't believe work today.
The mailing [music] station misplaced
three of my packages and it was my pay
that was docked.
>> Parcel Corp, put down your toys and get
ready for dinner. I'm not hungry. Don't
be like that. We all have to be on our
best behaviors since cousins Brayburn
and Saurin will be here [music] soon
with that bastard child of mine.
>> He's your half brother Puzzlecore. So,
learn to have fun with him.
>> But he has a gross clown fetish. We're
already here. [cheering and music]
Want to see my private balloon trick?
Saurin and Braburn said I shouldn't show
strangers but your family. So, it's
[music] fine. What you do with balloons
makes me uncomfortable.
>> No, we were never like this.
>> Tonight will be the night that I [music]
will fall for you.
>> Apple Bottom, will you turn that music
down? Shut up, [__]
>> Must you really call your mother a
[__]
>> This is closer. We had a moment like
this, but it wasn't all like this
either. What were we like again?
>> It doesn't matter. We're never going
back to our peaceful days together.
>> See, this is what he does. Are we just
going to act like we ever had peaceful
days to begin with?
>> I never wanted to break up with you. I
did it because I want you all to myself
and I didn't feel like you wanted the
same.
>> Of course, I want that, too. I'm in love
with how you can just be who you want in
a way society could never understand. I
admit it. I messed up by trying to show
you off. But you have to understand, I
only did that because when I look at
you, I see a version of myself I'll
never be able to become. I only feel
like my real self when I'm around you.
And wanting others to look at you was my
way of feeling proud of myself through
you.
What are you doing?
>> Every pony in Equestria is gone. We're
the only two left. There was never a
world where this could work. I can only
love in isolation. And with no pony left
for me to kill, I'm bored. So let me be
the last thing that disappears.
>> You just said there's no pony left in
Equestria. If you leave, won't I be the
one totally isolated then?
>> That's why it's a fitting end. We were
never going to have a normal, peaceful
ending. We're not like Saurin and
Brayburn.
>> Care package.
>> I never stopped loving you, Apple
Bottom. And I'll take that love to my
grave. I hope that you'll do the same
for me, too.
care package.
>> Saurin,
>> why did [music] I bring Apple Bottom
back to life if you were just going to
kill yourself?
>> How are you here?
>> Even though you and Apple Bottom are
always fighting over that knife, don't
forget it's my magic inside it. [music]
So when you absorb it, I can freely
appear in your mind whenever. When my
physical body died, I just ended up
here.
Don't you love him?
>> Of course I do.
>> Then quit making things so complicated.
If you keep breaking up with him in
attempts to manipulate [music] him,
eventually it's going to get to a point
that you ask yourself if your
relationship was ever really real.
>> What? What did you do?
>> If the alicorn of death can bring a pony
to the end of their lifespan, then it
only makes sense that the alicorn of
life can bring them back [music] to any
state of their life. I'm keeping you
here with me forever. I win.
>> Hold on. The alicorn of life forever,
then we'll be trapped in an endless
loop. You bring anyone else back, I'll
erase them over and over. Just [music]
the two of us destroying and rebuilding
reality as we see fit. Are you really
fine with that? I'm fine with it,
[music] but I know you couldn't be.
You'll get that itch to feel a
connection with someone again. You're
the one who needs others to feel
anything at all, not me. Even [music] if
that feeling is murdering them, that's
why you were only content to die once
everyone else was gone.
>> Don't.
>> And you don't have the heart to kill me.
Not again. It's why you had to break up
with me instead.
>> Stop.
>> Because you can't stand being truly
alone. So I'll bring them all back.
Every pony [music]
>> always
[music]
we can turn it all around in the end.
>> What the [__] is happening?
>> If we're going to play [music] the parts
of Overseers of life and death, let's
not be lonely when we don't have to be.
run
always shuns and push the [__] away.
>> But things are different now. It's show
[music]
I have a lot to catch you up on.
One more time.
[music]
So put your love in mine and look
every pony while that vampire is
dehydrated.
>> I know you think [music] I'm getting
strong.
Always fighting for somewhere.
[music]
We can turn it all around in the end.
It's not what you expect. We will
[music] always be connected.
>> So, it's absorbing all our magic. If
only there was somebody who could attack
it from behind.
>> Did some pony say behind?
>> Sunny Star Scout. We know all too well
what it's like to be behind someone
because Hasbro is literally leaving G5
behind right now in favor of what will
probably be Friendship of Magic
Nostalgia Bait or some [__] for the next
generation. So, let us do one last thing
before G5 is completely forgotten,
[__]
Dads, I'm a bit dehydrated out there.
I'm going to have to borrow some of your
blood if that's all right.
[music]
>> As your flesh and blood, all your
feelings are my own. You were just about
ready to die, weren't you? So, let me
have a bite.
>> No, I have someone to live for at the
moment. If you were really our child,
you'd know that. As it is now, I don't
even know where you came from.
>> [bell]
[music]
>> Brother, brother from another father, a
being that can't properly be killed is
best left to be enveloped in
nothingness.
Stop. Unhand me. Apple bottom care
package. Don't do this to me. I'm your
child. Just take me home and we can talk
about this.
>> [__] in this economy, stallions are
paid like 30 cents on the dollar that
marries.
>> Yeah, it's bad enough raising a horse
with the pay one's bringing home. Can
you imagine two?
>> [__] you. [__] you. [__] you. [__] you.
[__] all of you [__] [__] Don't
think you've seen the last of me, you
absolute pile of [__] stained, worthless
goddamn pieces of [__] I live in the
[__] dark, it's where I [__]
thrive, godamn it. When you miserable
little shits crawl into bed tonight and
turn off the lights. I'm the one under
your beds, you [__] bags. I'm the one
you see peeking out of your closets. The
darkness is the one afraid of me, not
the other way around. You're all nothing
but my goddamn [__] bags of
blood. And I'll drain you of all your
sweet, sweet ketchup until you've been
rung dry, you shitty, useless,
bloodstuffed bastards.
You know, Sombra, when my head was like
cut off, I had only a few seconds of
consciousness before everything went
black. And even in that time, I saw how
worried you were for me. My [__] of a
wife never cared for me like that.
>> What are you saying?
>> What I'm saying, Sombra, is you helped
me come to understand the term once you
go black, you never go back. I can't
ever seeing myself returning to my old
heteronormative lifestyle.
>> Hold up, baby girl. Do you do you really
mean that
>> with every fiber of my being?
>> Oh, I I I'm not interested in you
anymore then since since I'm into, you
know, straight guys, but I I'll wish you
the best of luck, I guess. I I got to go
now. See you around.
I almost made a mistake, Apple Bottom.
You are the one I cherish most in this
world, but that doesn't mean everyone
else has to be gone. I would like to get
back together with you if you would let
me.
>> I don't know. Since you broke up with
me, I've been living my best life. I'm
making more money and my relations to
the Apple family are better than they've
ever been. Celestia even made me an
alicorn and said I could keep this magic
if I killed you.
>> I never said that.
>> Why would I give all that up?
>> Because you love me.
>> If you want me back, you're going to
have to beg for it.
Plead for it like the lonely little
loser who can't survive a single night
without me. Say you want to marry me so
badly. Or would you rather be all alone
forever?
>> Please, please marry me. I can't breathe
without you, Apple Bottom. I can't do
these back and forths anymore. I need
you more than you need me. I need you
way more than you need me.
>> You sound real desperate. Look at you
shaking at my hooves. You really are
nothing without me, aren't you? Who's
going to be wearing the dress, I wonder?
It ain't a proper wedding unless one of
us is a groom and the other's a bride.
Wouldn't you agree?
>> I'll be the bride if that's what you
want. It doesn't matter to me. I'll do
it. I'll be the bride. I don't care.
Tell me what I have to look like.
>> [music]
>> Dad, isn't it humiliating seeing your
son in a wedding dress?
What are you doing here?
Every day with you is magic.
Every kiss is better than the last.
It's a home I've never [singing]
known.
A place I know will last.
for a lifetime [music]
of I love you.
Two hearts, one beat. You whisper
to me.
[singing]
>> You know, I've really always dreamed of
this day. That's not even a joke.
From the moment I met you, care package,
when you were delivering my ice cream
cones, I just knew we [music] would end
up here. You saved me from a horrible,
horrible situation, and I knew deep down
that you were going to change my life
forever. You looked at me in a way that
was something other than disgust, which
I've told you too many times before is
how everyone in my life had viewed me up
to that point. All the years I spent
feeling worthless suddenly didn't matter
because they led me to you. And somehow
you made up for every one of them. Since
then, you've become my favorite part
[music] of every day. You make the world
feel lighter when it gets too heavy. And
you've shown me what it truly means to
be loved. So today, standing here with
you, I want you to know
>> that the feeling I had that very first
moment, that absolute certainty that you
were the one for me is still here,
stronger than ever. And I promise for
the rest of my life, I'll keep choosing
you just like you chose me that first
day.
>> You didn't [music] tell me the vows were
going to be genuine.
I knew you wouldn't be humiliated by
something as little as a dress. The only
way I could get away with it is by being
completely genuine with you.
[music]
Cuz [music]
the world is for us. It doesn't matter
what we do. I feel [music]
>> he's giving you both one more shot at
life. So don't you waste it. Do anything
to make him sad again. And you're both
going back to the end of the road. Do
you understand?
>> Daddy, can you pass the salt?
I want to show you a neat [music] little
magic trick I learned. Watch me closely.
>> Wa, that's so convenient.
>> I am going to hold on to the both of
these from now on so you can have this
useless [music] one I bought at the
dollar store.
>> My life sucks.
Spitfire, how's [music] life been
treating you crazy [__] Well, if it
isn't the rainbow s blaster, are you
still working for the weather patrol
facility? When are you going to join the
Wonderbolts for real so you can be done
with that shitty 9 to5? You know,
Fluttershy would be bored without me.
That loser. Who gives a [__] about that
[__] Hey, Saurin.
>> Good news, y'all. I just wrangled up 37
tuidos for the Wonderbolts that we y'all
could chow down on before we set out.
Brain, we have a performance in 2 hours.
If we eat those, we are going to [__]
all over the crowd. Saurin, control your
boy.
>> I just wanted to be useful to the team.
>> Wow. Okay, first off, don't talk to my
boyfriend like that. He was being
thoughtful.
>> Do you want one, Saurin?
>> Well, she's she's not wrong, Brayburn.
We have [__] all over the crowd before,
and we constantly fear for a repeat
occurrence. But you can eat them. You
deserve them all for trying to be sweet.
Hey yo, Water Boy, go dump the
Wonderboat's piss and [__] barrel.
>> Thunderlane, stop calling him water boy.
Ain't nobody tells me what to do, [__]
ass [__] you're like twice my age, or
man, so take your boy and piss off.
>> Stop it.
>> Chill your balls, queer. It was an
accident.
All these snacks and I only want you for
a midday bite. How's that make you feel?
>> That's a terrible idea. You'll hurt your
teeth. You should eat chips instead.
>> No, I [music] meant a different kind of
bite. Something sweeter.
>> Then why are we standing by the chips?
The candy's over there. I can buy you
Skittles.
>> You [music] really don't get it.
>> I do get it. Apple Bottom, you're
craving sugar. Come along. I'll fix
that.
>> How did you know? I've been thirsting
for a sour green apple slushie all week.
>> I listen to what my little apple strudel
wants.
>> A medium like usual, right? [music]
>> Hey, if you do that gay little dance, I
love I just might let you go for the big
gulp. Aha. Yeah. Yes. Jolly good. You
just earned yourself a big gulp with
that one if you can handle it.
>> Oh, you know I can handle big things. My
greatest talent is working [music]
things I can wrap both hooves around.
>> Oh, I know that.
>> What the [__] is this care package?
They're all out of sour green apple. You
knew they were out, didn't you? You
[music] did this to humiliate me.
>> Just get cherry.
>> The apple family only eats apple themed
food. It's who we are. I can't be seen
drinking a cherry slushie. That would be
embarrassing.
>> You tell your [__] boyfriend, [__]
What's up, cousin Apple Bottom? Our
family makes money off any and every
apple themed product sold around these
here parts. So, support the family
business. Sar and cover my baby sister's
ears. Purchasing a cherry slushie is
giving money to the cherry family
[__]
Stop it. You are going to get a
concussion acting like that.
>> Put me down. I am the one in control of
my own life. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it.
Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. What
is it, Big Mac?
>> What the [__] do you think Sugar Cube Me
and Apple Bottom just found a slushie
that isn't selling sour green apple like
it's supposed to, and the establishment
ain't doing nothing about it?
>> Well, then what are you waiting for?
Break the goddamn mechanical
contraption?